Harold H. Burton Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Supreme Court File, 1792-1965 (Box 56-325)
  - Correspondence, 1936-1965 (Box 56-125)
    - October term 1947
      - “Po-Py” miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 76)
      - “Q” miscellaneous, 1947
      - Restrictive covenant cases, 1948, undated
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (2 folders)
      - Salvation Army, 1948
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1947-1948, (4 folders)
      - Sheets, William M., 1946-1948
      - Sipuel v. Board of Regents, 1948
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (3 folders)
      - Temple Law Quarterly, 1947-1948
      - “T-U” miscellaneous, 1946-1948, (2 folders)
      - Vacation, 1948-1949
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
      - West Publishing Co., 1947-1948 (Box 77)
      - Woods v. Miller, 1947-1948
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, (2 folders)
      - Yee-Quil, Cornelia N., 1947-1948
      - YMCA, 1947-1948
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1947-1948
    - October term 1948
      - All Souls' Church, Washington, D.C., 1948-1949
      - American Bar Association, 1948-1949
      - American Law Institute, Philadelphia, Pa., 1949
      - American Legion, 1948-1949
      - Army & Navy Union, U.S.A., Americanism Award, 1949, (2 folders)
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1948-1949
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (3 folders)
      - Caldwell, Russell L., 1946-1949
      - California trip, 1949
      - Cleveland Chamber of Commerce, Cleveland, Ohio, 1948-1949
      - Cleveland Crime Commission, Cleveland, Ohio, 1949
      - Comrades of the Purple Heart, 1948-1949
      - Condolences, 1949
      - Crank letters, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (4 folders)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1948-1949
      - “D” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
      - Edwards, William E., 1949
      - Ervin, James M., 1945-1949
      - “E-F” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (3 folders)
      - Gillespie, Margaret E., 1948-1949
      - Gruenig, Emil, 1948-1949
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1948-1949
      - Holmes, Harry A., 1947-1949
      - Hopper, Pariska, 1948-1949
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - Invitations accepted, 1948-1949
      - Invitations declined, 1948-1949
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1948-1949
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Shawnee-on-Delaware, Pa., 1948-1949
      - “J-K” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
      - Law clerks, applications, 1948-1949
      - Lawyers Co-operative Publishing Co., 1946-1949
      - Lebow, John A., 1946-1948
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
      - MacMorran, Lloyd H., 1948-1949
      - Mann, W. Howard, 1949
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (4 folders)
      - Ninety-First Division Association, 1948-1949
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 80)
      - Office of the Reporter, 1948-1949
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1948-1949
      - Patents, 1949
      - Pathfinders of America, Inc., Cleveland, Ohio, 1948-1949
      - Perlman, Philip B., 1948
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1948-1949
      - Publications ordered, 1948-1949
      - “P-R” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (5 folders)
      - Salvation Army, 1948-1949
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1948-1949, (4 folders)
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (3 folders)
      - Tinsley, Lelia M., 1949
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1948-1949
      - “U-V” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 81)
      - West Publishing Co., 1948-1949
      - Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio, 1948-1949
      - Weston, Harris K., 1948-1949
      - William D. Callaghan, Inc., Cleveland, Ohio, 1947-1949
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
      - YMCA, 1948-1949
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1948-1949
    - October term 1949
      - American Bar Association, 1950
      - American Legion, 1949-1950
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, New York, N.Y., 1949-1950
      - American Unitarian Association, 1949-1950
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Baily, Harold J., 1950
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1949-1950
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (3 folders)
      - Coman, Daniel J., 1949-1950
      - Condolences, 1949-1950
      - Crank letters
        - 1949
        - 1950 (Box 82)
      - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, board of elections, 1949-1950
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (4 folders)
      - Douglas, William O., 1949-1950
      - “D-E” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (3 folders)
      - Freemasons, 1949-1950
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - George Washington University Law School, Washington, D.C., 1949-1950
      - Grasselli, Harry W., 1949-1950
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Hart, Earl E., 1950
      - Henderson v. United States, 1952
      - “Hollywood Ten,” petitions, 1950
      - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1949-1950
      - Hughes, Charles Evans, regarding, 1948-1949
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (2 folders) (Box 83)
      - Invitations accepted, 1949-1950
      - Invitations declined, 1949-1950
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - Kinsman Jewish Center, Cleveland, Ohio, 1946-1950
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1950
        - Appointments, 1950
      - Library, Supreme Court, 1950
      - Lightner, Leo F., 1949-1950
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass., 1949-1950
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (4 folders)
      - National Association of Referees in Bankruptcy, 1949-1950 (Box 84)
      - Ninety-First Division reunions, 1947-1950
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Office of the Reporter, 1949-1950
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1950
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1950
      - Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity, 1949-1950
      - Portrait of Burton, Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass., 1950
      - “P” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (3 folders)
      - Ralston, George L., 1950
      - Reeder, Spencer W., 1949-1950
      - Rent control, 1949-1950
      - Retirement of judges, 1950
      - Richards, J. Noble, 1949-1950
      - Rubenstein, Bernard Joseph, 1949-1950
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Salaries, Supreme Court employees, 1949 (Box 85)
      - Salvation Army, 1949-1950
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1947-1950, (2 folders)
      - Smith, Betty, 1946-1950
      - Students, 1949-1950
      - Sturgis, Alice F., 1950
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (3 folders)
      - Tarnawa, Taras M., 1948-1950
      - “T-U” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - Volta Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1949-1950
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
      - Whyss, Imogene, 1949-1950
      - Williamson v. United States, 1950
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - YMCA, 1950 (Box 86)
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1949-1950
    - October term 1950
      - American Bar Association, 1950-1951
      - American Legion, 1950-1951
      - American Unitarian Association, 1950-1951
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (2 folders)
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1950-1951
      - Brandt, Herbert, 1950
      - Brewster, Owen, 1950-1951
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (3 folders)
      - Civil service status of Judiciary employees, 1950-1951
      - Communist leaders cases, 1950-1951
      - Condolences, 1950-1951
      - Crampton, Robert J., 1951
      - Crank letters, 1949-1951
      - “C-D” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (3 folders)
      - Edwards, Gerald E., 1946-1951
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
      - Fake, Guy L., 1950 (Box 87)
      - Frankfurter, Felix, 1951
      - Freemasons, 1950-1951
      - “F-G” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (3 folders)
      - Hart, Earl E., 1950-1951
      - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1950-1951
      - Howe, Edwin A., 1951
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (2 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1950-1951
      - Invitations declined, 1950-1951
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1951
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1950-1951, (2 folders)
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
      - Kappa Beta Pi Legal Sorority convention, Miami, Fla., 1951
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1951, (2 folders)
        - Appointments, 1951
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (2 folders) (Box 88)
      - MacMorran, Lloyd H., 1951
      - Maine Development Commission, Augusta, Maine, luncheon, 1951
      - Mann, W. Howard, 1950-1951
      - “Martinsville Seven,” rape cases, 1951
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass., 1950-1951
      - McGee, Willie, re stay of execution, 1950-1951
      - Miller, Locke, re Miller v. Kosling, 1950-1951
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (2 folders)
      - Ninety-First Division Association, 1950-1951
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1949-1951, (2 folders)
      - Office of the Reporter, 1950-1951
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
      - Pathfinders of America, Inc., Cleveland, Ohio, 1950-1951
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1950-1951
      - “P” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
      - Reeder, Spencer W., 1950-1951
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
      - Salvation Army, 1950-1951
      - Sessions, Gilpin S.
        - 1950
        - 1951, (4 folders) (Box 89)
      - Strait, P. L., 1949-1951
      - Supreme Court building, inscriptions and sculpture
      - “S-V” miscellaneous, 1950-1951, (5 folders)
      - Waltz, Jon, 1950-1951
      - Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio, 1949-1951
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
      - YMCA, 1950-1951
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1950-1951
    - October term 1951
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1951-1952
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1951-1952
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (2 folders) (Box 90)
      - Clothey, Thomas L., 1951-1952
      - Condolences, 1951-1952
      - Cornell, Fred A., 1945, 1951-1952
      - Crank letters, 1951-1952, undated, (2 folders)
      - “C-E” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (6 folders)
      - Frankfurter, Felix, 1951-1952, undated
      - Freemasons, 1951-1952
      - “F-G” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
      - Hayek, Henry R., 1952
      - Hendel, Samuel, 1951-1952
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1951-1952 (Box 91)
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1952
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1951-1952
      - Judicial Conference of the Tenth Circuit, Denver, Colo., 1952
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
      - Krahnstoever, Felix, 1951-1952
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1951-1952
        - Appointments, 1951-1952
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass., 1951-1952
      - “M-N” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (3 folders)
      - Office of the Reporter, 1951-1952
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1951-1952
      - Pittman, R. Carter, 1951-1952
      - Publications ordered, 1951-1952
      - Publications received, 1952
      - “Pa-Pf” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
      - “Ph-Py” miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 92)
      - Ramaswamy, M., 1949-1952
      - Rubenstein, Bernard Joseph, 1951-1952
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
      - Salvation Army, 1952
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1951-1952, (4 folders)
      - Shotter, Carl L., 1950-1952
      - Smith, Reginald Heber, 1951-1952
      - Steel seizure cases, 1952, undated, (3 folders)
      - “S-U” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (5 folders)
      - Vacation, 1952
      - Vinson, Fred M., 1951-1952
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
      - Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio, 1952
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1951-1952, (2 folders) (Box 93)
      - YMCA, 1951-1952
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1951-1952
    - October term 1952
      - American Bar Association, 1952-1953
      - American Legion, 1949-1953
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1952-1953
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (3 folders)
      - Beta Sigma Phi, 1953
      - Birthday greetings, 1952-1953
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1952-1953
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (4 folders)
      - Christmas greetings, 1952-1953
      - Cleveland Bar Association, Cleveland, Ohio, 1953
      - Condolences, 1952-1953
      - Crank letters, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - Cuyahoga County, Ohio, board of elections, 1953
      - “C-D” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (6 folders) (Box 94)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight D., inauguration ceremonies, 1952-1953
      - Essex County Bar Association, Newark, N.J., 1953
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1952-1953
      - Frankfurter, Felix, 1952-1953
      - Freemasons, 1952-1953
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (4 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
      - Invitations declined, 1952-1953
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1952-1953
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1952-1953
      - “J-K” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (3 folders)
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1951-1953
        - Former, 1952-1953
      - “L-M” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (6 folders)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1952-1953
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - Office of the Reporter, 1952-1953 (Box 96)
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1952-1953
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1952-1953
      - Portrait ceremony, Fenn College, Cleveland, Ohio, 1953
      - Publications received, 1952-1953
      - “P-Q” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (3 folders)
      - Rosenberg, Ethel and Julius, trial and execution, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - Salvation Army, 1953
      - Segregation cases, 1952-1953, undated
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1952-1953, (5 folders)
      - Students, meetings with, 1953
      - Supreme Court building, memorial plaque, 1952-1953 (Box 97)
      - “S-T” miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (5 folders)
      - University of Toledo, Toledo, Ohio, 1953
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1952-1953
      - Volta Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1952-1953
      - “V-W” miscellaneous, 1952-1954, (3 folders)
      - YMCA, 1952-1953
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1952-1953
    - October term 1953
      - Administrative Office of the United States Courts, Washington, D.C., 1954
      - American Bar Association, 1954
      - American Legion, 1954
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1953-1954
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1953-1954
      - Birthday greetings, 1954
      - Bolton, Frances P., 1954 (Box 98)
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1953-1954, (3 folders)
      - Clothey, Thomas L., 1954
      - College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Va., 1954
      - Commission on Judicial and Congressional Salaries, Washington, D.C., 1953-1954
      - Condolences, 1954, undated
      - Crank letters, 1954, undated
      - “C-E” miscellaneous, 1949-1954, (6 folders)
      - Frankfurter, Felix, 1954
      - Freemasons, 1954
      - “F-H” miscellaneous, 1954, (4 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1953-1954 (Box 99)
      - Invitations declined, 1954
      - Iota Theta Law Fraternity, banquet, New York, N.Y., 1953-1954
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1954
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit
        - Atlantic City, N.J., 1953-1954
        - Philadelphia, Pa., 1954-1955
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1953-1954
      - Kubota, Kinuko, 1952-1954
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1954
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1953-1954
        - Appointments, 1953-1954
      - “L-N” miscellaneous, 1954, (6 folders)
      - Office of the Clerk, 1953-1954
      - Office of the Reporter, 1954
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1954
      - Pestalozzi Foundation, 1954 (Box 100)
      - Publications received, 1954
      - “P-Q” miscellaneous, 1953-1954, (2 folders)
      - Rubenstein, Bernard Joseph, 1954, undated
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1954
      - Salvation Army, 1954
      - Segregation cases, 1953-1954, undated, (6 folders)
      - Sessions, Gilbert S., 1953-1954, (4 folders)
      - Student Legal Forum, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Va., 1954
      - Students, meetings with, 1954
      - “Sa-Sm” miscellaneous, 1954, (2 folders)
      - “So-Sy” miscellaneous, 1953-1954, undated (Box 101)
      - “T-U” miscellaneous, 1951-1955, (2 folders)
      - Volta Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1954
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1954
      - Warren, Earl, 1953-1954
      - “W-Z” miscellaneous, 1953-1954, undated, (4 folders)
    - October term 1954
      - Administrative Office of the United States Courts, Washington, D.C., 1955
      - American Bar Association, 1955
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1954-1955
      - American Society of International Law, 1955
      - Arnold, Stanley N., 1954-1955
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1955
      - Birthday greetings, 1955
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1955, (3 folders)
      - Condolences, 1955, undated
      - Conference on Government under Law, Harvard Law School, Cambridge, Mass., 1955
      - Constitution Day, Silver Spring, Md., 1955
      - Crank letters, 1955, undated
      - “C-E” miscellaneous, 1955, undated, (6 folders) (Box 102)
      - Fordham Law Review
      - Frankfurter, Felix, 1955, undated
      - Freemasons, 1956
      - “F-H” miscellaneous, 1954-1956, (4 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1954-1955
      - Invitations declined, 1955
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1955
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1955
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1955
      - King, Willard L., re Ex parte Milligan
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1955
      - Law clerks (Box 103)
        - Applications, 1954-1955
        - Appointments, 1955
        - Reunion, 1954-1955, (2 folders)
      - Lingelbach, Louis, 1955
      - “L-M” miscellaneous, 1955, undated, (5 folders)
      - Newton High School, Newtonville, Mass., 1905, 1954-1955
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1955
      - Office of the Clerk, 1954-1955
      - Office of the Reporter, 1955
      - Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio, 1954-1955
      - O'Neill, Thomas N., 1955, undated
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1955
      - Publications received, 1955
      - “P” miscellaneous, 1955, (2 folders)
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1955
      - Salvation Army, 1955
      - Segregation cases, 1954-1955, undated, (5 folders) (Box 104)
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1954-1955, (2 folders)
      - State Bar of Michigan, Lansing, Mich., 1955
      - Students, meetings with, 1955
      - Switzerland, family and friends, 1953-1955, undated, (2 folders)
      - “S” miscellaneous, 1955, (2 folders)
      - Thompson, George Jarvis, 1955
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1955
      - University of Michigan Law School, Ann Arbor, Mich., 1954-1955
      - “U” miscellaneous, 1954-1955
      - Vacation, 1955
      - Volta Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1954-1955
      - “V” miscellaneous, 1955
      - Warren, Earl, 1954-1955 (Box 105)
      - Wolfe, Paul C., 1955
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1955, undated, (2 folders)
      - YMCA, 1955
      - “Y-Z” miscellaneous, 1955
    - October term 1955
      - American Bar Association, 1955-1956
      - American Hospital Association, 1956
      - American Legion, 1955-1956
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1956
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders)
      - Birthday greetings, 1956
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders)
      - Condolences, 1956, undated
      - Court of Nisi Prius, Cleveland, Ohio, 1956
      - Crank letters, 1955-1956
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders)
      - Denison University, Granville, Ohio, 1956
      - Denman, William, 1956
      - “D-E” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders)
      - Federal rules of civil procedure, 1955-1956 (Box 106)
      - Frankfurter, Felix, 1955-1956
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1955-1956
      - Gearty, William J., 1956
      - “G-H” miscellaneous, 1956, (3 folders)
      - Ihlder, John, testimonial dinner, 1956
      - Invitations accepted, 1955-1956, (2 folders)
      - Invitations declined, 1956
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1955-1956
      - Judicial Conference of the Third Circuit, Atlantic City, N.J., 1956
      - Judicial Conference of the Fourth Circuit, Hot Springs, Va., 1956
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1956
      - Kappa Beta Pi Legal Sorority International, 1956
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders)
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1955-1956
        - Appointments, 1956
        - Former, 1956
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders)
      - “Ma” miscellaneous, 1956
      - “Mc-My” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders) (Box 107)
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1956
      - Office of the Clerk, 1956
      - Office of the Reporter, 1956
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1956
      - Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity, 1955-1956
      - Publications received, 1956
      - “P-Q” miscellaneous, 1954-1956
      - Rubenstein, Bernard Joseph, 1956
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1956, (2 folders)
      - Students
        - Geneva, Ala., 1956
        - Meetings with, 1956, (2 folders)
      - Segregation cases, 1955-1956, undated, (3 folders)
      - Sessions, Gilpin S., 1955
      - Switzerland, family and friends, 1955-1956, (2 folders)
      - “S-U” miscellaneous, 1956, undated, (5 folders) (Box 108)
      - Vacation, 1955-1957, (2 folders)
      - Volta Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1956
      - “V” miscellaneous
      - Warren, Earl, 1956
      - “W-Z” miscellaneous, 1956, (3 folders)
    - October term 1956
      - American Bar Association, 1957
      - American Legion, 1957
      - American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1957
      - American Society for Legal History, 1956-1957
      - Arnold, Stanley N., 1956-1957
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Birthday greetings, 1957
      - Bricker, John W., 1957
      - “Ba-Bo” miscellaneous, 1956-1957, (2 folders)
      - “Br-By” miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 109)
      - Cincinnati Bar Association, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1957
      - Clark, Thomas C., 1957
      - Condolences, 1957, undated
      - Crank letters, 1956-1957, undated
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1957, (2 folders)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1956-1957
      - “D-E” miscellaneous, 1957, (2 folders)
      - Frankfurter, Felix, 1957
      - Fulton, Hugh, 1957
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Gregory, Eleanor, 1955-1957
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Hotel Cleveland, Cleveland, Ohio, 1957
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1957, (2 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, 1956-1957
      - Invitations declined, 1957
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Judicial Conference of the Sixth Circuit, Ann Arbor, Mich., 1957 (Box 110)
      - Judicial Conference of the Seventh Circuit, Chicago, Ill., 1957
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Knight, A. R., 1957
      - “K” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Law clerks
        - Applications, 1956-1957, (2 folders)
        - Appointments, 1957
      - Luncheon for members of the Court, 1955-1957
      - “L-M” miscellaneous, 1956-1957, (4 folders)
      - National Broadcasting Co., 1957
      - New Century Club, Wilmington, Del., 1956-1957
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Office of the Clerk, 1956
      - Office of the Reporter, 1957
      - Opinions by the Court, reaction to, 1957-1958, undated
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Publications acknowledged, 1957
      - “P-Q” miscellaneous, 1957
      - Rubenstein, Bernard Joseph, 1957
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 111)
      - Segregation cases, 1956-1957, undated, (3 folders)
      - Students, meetings with, 1957
      - “S-T” miscellaneous, 1956-1957, (4 folders)